<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.discover.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">استكشف</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Avastusretk</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Discoperi</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">살펴보기</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Ontdekken</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਖੋਜੋ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Odkrywca</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Центр приложений Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Objaviť</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Oткривач</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Otkrivač</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Oткривач</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Otkrivač</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Keşfet</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Discover</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxDiscoverxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">发现</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Discover</name>
  <summary>Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">استكشف</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Avastusretk</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Discoperi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">살펴보기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Ontdekken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਖੋਜੋ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Odkrywca</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Центр приложений Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Objaviť</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Oткривач</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Otkrivač</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Oткривач</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Otkrivač</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Keşfet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Discover</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxDiscoverxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">发现</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">Discover</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Have you ever found a tool that was perfect for your needs but you only found it after some time searching around the net? When trying to install an application, do you wonder if it’s really worth the effort? Or if it’s actually what you’re looking for?</p>
    <p>Discover helps users easily and quickly find applications or tools. By helping to navigate software collections by search, categories, top lists along with detailed application information that includes screenshots and reviews, users can more quickly find applications that suit their needs.</p>
    <p>Furthermore, Discover will let you manage the different sources of software you have and manage the applications you’ve already installed in the past but you don’t want anymore.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">عدا عن هذا كلّه، يتيح لك «استكشف» إدارة مختلف مصادر البرمجيّات التي لديك كما وإدارة التّطبيقات المثبّتة والتي لم تعد تحتاجها بعد الآن.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Per altra banda, el Discover permet gestionar les diferents fonts de programari que tingueu i gestionar les aplicacions que ja heu instal·lat en el passat però ja no desitgeu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Per altra banda, el Discover permet gestionar les diferents fonts de programari que tingueu i gestionar les aplicacions que ja heu instal·lat en el passat però ja no desitgeu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Desuden vil Discover lade dig håndtere dine forskellige softwarekilder og håndtere de programmer du allerede tidligere har installeret, men som du ikke længere ønsker.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Darüber hinaus können Sie mit Discover Ihre verschiedenen Softwarequellen verwalten sowie auch die Anwendungen, die Sie früher bereits installiert haben, aber nicht mehr verwenden möchten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Furthermore, Discover will let you manage the different sources of software you have and manage the applications you have already installed in the past but you do not want any more.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Además, Discover le permite gestionar las distintas fuentes de software de las que disponga y las aplicaciones que ya hubiera instalado en el pasado y que ya no desee.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Lisaks laseb Avastusretk sul mitmekülgselt hallata kõiki sinu käsutuses olevaid tarkvaraallikaid ega jäta sind hätta ka siis, kui sul leidub tarkvara, mille oled kunagi paigaldanud, aga enam sugugi ei vaja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Honetaz gain, Discover-rek dituzun software iturburu desberdinak kudeatzen utziko dizu eta iraganean instalatu zenituen baino gehiago nahi ez dituzun aplikazioak kudeatzen utziko dizu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Discover sallii sinun lisäksi hallita erilaisia ohjelmalähteitä sekä sovelluksia, jotka olet jo asentanut mutta joita et enää halua.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">De plus, Discover vous permet de gérer les différentes sources de logiciels que vous avez et permet de gérer les applications que vous avez installé par le passé et que vous ne voulez plus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Ademais, Discover permitiralle xestionar as distintas fontes de software de que dispón e xestionar os aplicativos que ten instalados pero que xa non lle interesan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Selanjutnya, Discover akan membiarkan Anda mengelola sumber software yang berbeda-beda yang Anda miliki dan mengelola aplikasi yang sudah Anda instal di masa lalu tetapi Anda tidak menginginkannya lagi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Inoltre, Discover ti consentirà di gestire le diverse fonti del software disponibili e gestire le applicazioni che hai già installato in passato, ma che non ti servono più.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">발견을 통하여 여러 소프트웨어 저장소를 관리하고 이전에 설치했지만 필요하지 않은 프로그램을 관리할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Verder laat Discover u de verschillende bronnen van software die u hebt beheren, evenals de al eerder geïnstalleerde toepassingen maar die u niet meer wilt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Du får òg kontroll over dei ulike programvarekjeldene du har, og kan lett avinstallera program du tidlegare har installert men som du ikkje lenger treng.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dodatkowo, Odkrywca umożliwia zarządzanie wieloma źródłami oprogramowania i oprogramowaniem, które jest już na twoim komputerze i którego chcesz się pozbyć.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Para além disso, o Discover permitir-lhe-á gerir as diferentes fontes de aplicações que tem e gerir as aplicações que já instalou no passado e que não quer mais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Além disso, o Discover possibilita gerenciar as diferentes fontes de software que você possui e os aplicativos que já foram instalados e que não são mais necessários.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Кроме того, центр приложений Discover позволяет управлять источниками приложений, а также выполнять удаление ненужных приложений.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Okrem toho, Discover vám umožní spracovať rôzne zdroje softvéru a spravovať aplikácie, ktoré máte nainštalované, ale už ich nechcete.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Discover vam tudi omogoča upravljati s programskimi viri in že nameščenimi programi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Затим, Oткривач вам омогућава да управљате различитим изворима софтвера, као и програмима које сте инсталирали раније али их више не желите.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Zatim, Otkrivač vam omogućava da upravljate različitim izvorima softvera, kao i programima koje ste instalirali ranije ali ih više ne želite.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Затим, Oткривач вам омогућава да управљате различитим изворима софтвера, као и програмима које сте инсталирали раније али их више не желите.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Zatim, Otkrivač vam omogućava da upravljate različitim izvorima softvera, kao i programima koje ste instalirali ranije ali ih više ne želite.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Dessutom låter Discover dig hantera olika programvarukällor du använder och hantera program som du redan tidigare har installerat men inte lägre vill ha.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Dahası, Keşfet, geçmişte yüklediğiniz fakat artık ihtiyacınız olmayan uygulamaları yönetmenize de olanak sağlar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Крім того, Discover надасть вам змогу керувати різними джерелами програмного забезпечення та вилучати програми, у яких уже немає потреби.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFurthermore, Discover will let you manage the different sources of software you have and manage the applications you’ve already installed in the past but you don’t want anymore.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">进一步，发现还可以管理多个不同软件源并且管理过去已安装但不再需要的程序。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">此外，Discover 讓您管理您所擁有的不同的軟體來源，也可以管理您以前安裝，但現在並不想要了的應用程式。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=Discover</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Plasma Discover</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/plasma-discover/plasma-discover.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>plasma-discover</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="5.15.4" date="2019-04-02"/>
    <release version="5.15.90" date="2019-05-16"/>
  </releases>
</component>
